A Guide to the Tom Buckley Collection on Virginia Political Campaign Memorabilia, 1963-2009 (bulk 1969-1983)
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
The Tom Buckley Collection on Virginia Political Campaign Memorabilia, 1963-2009 (bulk 1969-1983)
Fairfax County Public Library
MSS 06-94
5.5 linear feet
The Tom Buckley Collection consists of 5.5 linear feet spanning the years 1963-2009 (bulk 1969-1983), contains political pamphlets, newsletters, sample ballots, bumper stickers and other campaign stickers, buttons, posters, and various campaign paraphernalia.
Buckley, Tom
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
None
Acquisition Information
Donated by Tom Buckley, August 2017
Historical and Biographical Information
Tom Buckley grew up in Fairfax County and graduated from Hayfield Secondary School in 1973. He was active in Virginia politics from 1973-1983, working in many local and statewide political campaigns, both as a staffer and volunteer. He was a member of the Fairfax County Democratic Committee and worked in the field and advance operations for Congressman Herb Harris from 1974-1982, was the 8th District Field Director for Henry Howell for Governor in 1977, and assisted in many House of Delegates, State Senate, and Fairfax County campaigns. Tom left Virginia in 1983 for the District of Columbia where he has been employed at WUSA9 as a studio technician for over 40 years.
Scope and Content
The Tom Buckley Collection consists of 5.5 linear feet spanning the years 1963-2009 (bulk 1969-1983), contains political pamphlets, newsletters, sample ballots, bumper stickers and other campaign stickers, buttons, posters, and various campaign paraphernalia. The materials relate primarily to local (particularly Fairfax City and Fairfax County offices) campaigns, Virginia state legislature races, and Congressional campaigns in Northern Virginia. In addition, the collection contains materials from state-wide Virginia and Presidential campaigns. Offices represented include Fairfax County Board of Supervisors, Fairfax City Sheriff, Commonwealth Attorney, House of Delegates, State Senate, Governor, Lieutenant Governor, Attorney General, U.S. House of Representatives, U.S. Senate, and President. Candidates from the Democratic and Republican parties as well as some independent candidates are represented. The majority of the materials are for Democratic candidates.
Materials are organized within each Series primarily by individual candidate. A candidate’s materials are filed together regardless of the number of campaigns or offices that he or she ran in. Materials related to multiple candidates are filed at the end of each series by level of office and date of the campaign. “Election - General” designates materials that include candidates from multiple levels. “Election - Virginia” designates materials for multiple candidates running on a state-wide ticket, such as Governor, Lieutenant Governor, and Attorney General. “Election - Local Issues” designates materials related to local issues such as bonds for schools or parks.
Materials related primarily to political party activities are filed under the name of the party, e.g., “Election - Democratic Party”. Local offices are for Fairfax City or Fairfax County unless stated otherwise, e.g. Arlington County Board of Supervisors.
Series 1: Pamphlets, 1963-2009, Boxes 1-7
This series contains paper documents which include pamphlets, brochures, newsletters, broadsheets, sample ballots, and matchbook covers related to local (Fairfax City and Fairfax County), state, and national political campaigns. Candidates with substantial materials include Herbert E. Harris, II (House of Representatives), Henry E. Howell, Jr. (Governor) and Andrew P. Miller (Attorney General, Governor, U.S. Senate). The collection also includes a brochure from George Wallace’s 1968 Presidential campaign.
Series 2: Bumper stickers, 1965-2009, Boxes 7-9
This series contains bumper stickers and other campaign-related stickers related to local (Fairfax City and Fairfax County), state and national political campaigns.
Series 3: Buttons, 1963-1994, Boxes 9-11
This series contains campaign buttons and pins related to local (Fairfax City and Fairfax County), state and national political campaigns. (Be aware that many of these buttons still have the pins attached so handle carefully!) Notable materials include Henry E. Howell, Jr. buttons with a variety of slogans and “shoeprint” pins for Ira M. Lechner’s 1977 “the candidate who walked across Virginia” campaign for Lieutenant Governor.
Series 4: Posters, 1966-1994, Oversize Drawers
This series contains posters related to local (Fairfax City and Fairfax County), state and national political campaigns. Posters are filed alphabetically by name of the candidate.
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Virginia Room Election Files
None
Index Terms
Elections - Virginia; Elections - Virginia - Fairfax County; Fairfax County (Va.) - Politics and government; Political culture - Virginia; Virginia - Politics and government
Container List
- Series 1: Pamphlets, 1963-2009
  - Harold W. Adams (Delegate), 1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - John W. Adams, Jr. (Delegate), 1979 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - F. Keith Adkinson (Delegate), 1973 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Joseph Alexander (Board of Supervisors), 1974-1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - George F. Allen (Governor), 1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - James F. Almand (Delegate), 1977 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Hunter B. Andrews (U.S. Senate), 1978 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Robert T. Andrews (Delegate), 1981 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Terry C. Armstrong (Sheriff), 1979 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Arthur W. Arundel (State Senate), 1965 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - R. Barry Ashby (Delegate), 1971 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Frederick A. Babson, Jr. (Chair-Board of Supervisors, U.S. Senate), 1967-1977 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Richard M. Bagley (Governor), 1984 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Gerald L. Baliles (Attorney General, Governor), 1981-1985 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Warren E. Barry (Delegate), Undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - William C. Battle (Governor), 1969 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - John N. Beall, Jr. (State Senate), Undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Harry L. Bedsworth (Board of Supervisors), 1975-1979 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Belden H. Bell (Delegate), 1979 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Pixie Bell (Eighth Congressional District Democratic Committee), Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Nancy D. Bennett (Delegate), 1979 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Walter S. Boone, Jr. (Chair-Board of Supervisors), 1970 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - James B. Boren (House of Representatives), 1986 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Scott R. Bowden (House of Representatives), 1982 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Ellen M. Bozman (Arlington Board of Supervisors), 1973 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Adelard L. "Abe" Brault (State Senate), Undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - David C. Brickley (House of Representatives), 1988 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Doug Brooks (Delegate), Undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Joel T. Broyhill (House of Representatives), Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Dean E. Brundage (Delegate), 1979 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - John S. Buckley (Delegate), Undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Jim Burch (Delegate), 1971 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - John B. Burkel (Sheriff), Undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Kurt Burkhart (Eighth Congressional District Democratic Committee), 1976 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - George H.W. Bush (President), 1988 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Harry F. Byrd, Jr. (U.S. Senate), Undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Leslie L. Byrne (House of Representatives), 1994 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Jelks Henry Cabaniss, Jr. (Delegate), 1975 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Thomas R. Cagley (Delegate), 1977 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Mary F. Cahill (Delegate), 1973 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Charles Aubrey Callahan (Commissioner of the Revenue), 1965 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Vincent F. Callahan, Jr. (Delegate), Undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Richard W. Calvert (State Senate), 1979 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - A.J. "Joe" Canada, Jr. (Lieutenant Governor), 1977 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Jimmy Carter (President), 1976 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - J.J. "Jack" Caussin (Delegate), 1983 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Philip L. Chabot, Jr. (Delegate), 1983 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Warren I. Cikins (Board of Supervisors), Undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Lawrence S. Clark (Eighth Congressional District Democratic Committee), 1974 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Robert R. Cochrane (State Auditor), Undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Gwendalyn F. Cody (Delegate), 1981 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Charles E. Coe (House of Representatives, Board of Supervisors), 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Bernard S. Cohen (Delegate), 1981 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - J. Marshall Coleman (Attorney General, Governor), 1977-1981 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Theodore H. Collins (Commonwealth Attorney), Undated (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Craig G. Coverdale (House of Representatives), 1984 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Frances L. Cox (City Treasurer), 1977 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Flora M. Crater (Delegate), 1981 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Eason Cross (Board of Supervisors), 1975 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Nancy Cuddy (Board of Supervisors), Undated (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Robert K. Cunningham (Delegate), 1983 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - John N. Dalton, Jr. (Governor), 1977 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Gilbert K. Davis (Commonwealth Attorney), 1975 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Richard J. Davis (Lieutenant Governor, U.S. Senate), 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Thomas M. Davis, III (Board of Supervisors), 1979 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Warren J. Davis (Delegate), 1971 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - H. Dunlop "Buz" Dawbarn (Lieutenant Governor), 1969 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - James M. Day (Delegate), Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - James H. Dillard, II (Delegate), Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Richard E. Dixon (Board of Supervisors), Undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Eileen K. Donais (Delegate), 1983 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Andrew J. Donnelly (State Senate), 1971 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Sandra L. Duckworth (Board of Supervisors), 1975-1983 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Michael S. Dukakis (President), 1988 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - William R. Durland (Delegate, House of Representatives), 1965-1972 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - William R. Durrer (Board of Supervisors), 1975 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Wyatt B. Durrette (Attorney General), 1981 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Clive L. Duval, II (Delegate, House of Representatives, U.S. Senate, State Senate), Undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - T. Farrell Egge (House of Representatives, Board of Supervisors), 1976-1984 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Gary P. Eklund (Delegate), 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Dudley J. "Buzz" Emick, Jr. (Lieutenant Governor), 1981 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Carl Ericson (Board of Supervisors), 1979 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - A. Lee "Skip" Evans (City Democratic Committee), 1965 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Paula C. Faraday (Delegate), 1977 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Guy O. Farley (Attorney General, Delegate), 1963-1969 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Michael P. Farris (Lieutenant Governor), 1993 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Lester A. Fettig (Delegate), Undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Joseph L. Fisher (Arlington County Board of Supervisors, House of Representatives), Undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Robert C. Fitzgerald (State Senate), 1965 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Harry S. Flemming (Delegate), Undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Gerald R. Ford (President), 1976 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Lorraine F. Foulds (Clerk of Court), 1975 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Howard E. Futch (Board of Supervisors), 1975 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - David Gardner (House of Representatives), 1970 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Ray L. Garland (U.S. Senate), 1970 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Joseph V. Gartlan, Jr. (State Senate), Undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Richard H. Gentry (State Senate), 1967 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Mark L. Glaser (Delegate), 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Mills E. Godwin, Jr. (Governor), 1973 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Linda Golodner (Board of Supervisors), 1984 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - W. Franklin Gooding (Clerk of Court), 1967 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Bruce Green (Delegate), 1983 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Myron L. "Bud" Greenquist (Sheriff), 1979 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Dennis Gregg (House of Representatives), 1974 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Roger C. Grooms (Delegate), 1979 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Peter T. Halpin (Delegate-Democratic National Convention), 1976 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Herbert E. Harris, II (House of Representatives) (Folder 1 of 3), Undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Herbert E. Harris, II (House of Representatives) (Folder 2 of 3), Undated (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Herbert E. Harris, II (House of Representatives) (Folder 3 of 3), Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Robert E. Harris (Delegate), Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Edythe C. Harrison (U.S. Senate), 1984 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Elise B. Heinz (Delegate), 1977 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Horace Henderson (U.S. Senate), 1972 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Donald B. Henretty (Delegate), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - John F. "Jack" Herrity (Chair-Board of Supervisors, House of Representatives), Undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - M.J. "Mike" Hershman (Delegate), 1981 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - C.F. "Flip" Hicks (Attorney General), 1969 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Betsy W. Hinkle (Board of Supervisors), 1979 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Omer L. Hirst (State Senate), Undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Pat Holland (Alexandria Sheriff), Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Jon D. Holstine (Board of Supervisors), 1979 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Linwood Holton (Governor), 1969 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - James Hoofnagle (Clerk of Court), Undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - William S. Hoofnagle (Chair-Board of Supervisors), 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Robert F. Horan, Jr. (Commonwealth Attorney, House of Representatives), Undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Henry E. Howell, Jr. (Governor), Undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Karetta B. Hubbard (Delegate), 1977 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Maya A. Huber (Board of Supervisors), Undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - M. Wayne Huggins (Sheriff), 1979 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Gerald W. Hyland (Delegate, Board of Supervisors), Undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Nelson P. Jackson (Delegate), 1981 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Francis S. Jeffrey (Board of Supervisors), Undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Vivian Kallen (Delegate), 1969 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Charles E. Kaufman (Delegate), 1979 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Gladys B. Keating (Delegate), Undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Frank J. Kelly (House of Representatives), 1976 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - John E. Kennehan (Delegate), 1967 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Edward Kennedy (President), 1980 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Jane M. King (Delegate), 1979 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - David B. Kinney (House of Representatives), 1968 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Marilyn Klein (Board of Supervisors), Undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - George J. Kostel (Lieutenant Governor), 1971 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Roger Lee Kreuzer (Board of Supervisors), Undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Robert H. Kruhm (Delegate-Democratic National Convention), 1976 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Frank J. Kuhn, Jr. (State Senate), 1975 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Elaine A. Lailas (Delegate), 1981 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Harvey R. Lampshire (State Senate), 1965 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - George C. Landrith, Jr. (Delegate), 1981 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Edward E. Lane (Attorney General), 1977 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Charles B. Lankford (Sheriff), 1975 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Michael Patrick Leahy (Delegate), 1977 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Ira M. Lechner (Lieutenant Governor, House of Representatives), 1977-1982 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Ginny Lehner (Eighth Congressional District Democratic Committee), 1976 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Alice M. Leonard (Eighth Congressional District Democratic Committee), 1976 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Bernard Levin (Attorney General), 1969 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - William Marion Lightsey (Delegate), 1969 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Carolyn G. Lindberg (Delegate), 1971 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Edwin Lynch (Delegate-Democratic National Convention), 1976 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Henry C. Mackall (Delegate, State Senate), 1969-1971 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Alan H. Magazine (Board of Supervisors), 1971 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Charles Majer (Board of Supervisors), 1967 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Frank E. Mann (House of Representatives), 1974 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Joseph Marino (Delegate), 1979 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Conrad J. Marshall (Delegate), 1981 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Mary A. Marshall (Delegate), 1965 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - James C. Martinelli (Chair-Board of Supervisors), 1967 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Alison May (Alexandria City Council), 1970 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Randolph J. May (Delegate), 1975 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Andrew H. McCutcheon (House of Representatives), 1968 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Dorothy S. McDiarmid (Delegate, House of Representatives), Undated (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Virginia McEnearney (Board of Supervisors), 1973 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - George McGovern (President), 1972 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Kyle E. McSlarrow (House of Representatives), 1992-1994 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Frank Medico (Delegate), 1982 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Kenneth A. Meiklejohn (Chair-Fairfax County Democratic Committee), 1975 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - John L. Melnick (Attorney General), 1977 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Andrew P. Miller (Attorney General, Governor, U.S. Senate), 1969-1978 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Emilie F. Miller (State Senate), 1983 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Harold O. Miller (House of Representatives), 1972 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - James M. Miller (Delegate), 1965 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Ned D. Moore (Clerk of Court), Undated (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Nathan H. Miller (Lieutenant Governor), 1981 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - M. Lee Minnis (Delegate), 1979 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Myron Mintz (Board of Supervisors), 1971 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Perry Mitchell (U.S. Senate), 1976 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Robert L. Montague (Delegate, Attorney General), Undated (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Audrey C. Moore (Board of Supervisors, Chair-Board of Supervisors), Undated (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Brian J. Moran (Governor), 2009 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - James P. Moran, Jr. (House of Representatives), Undated (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - M.F. "Mike" Morris (Delegate), 1979 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Arthur Morrissette (Delegate), Undated (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Dennis Patrick "Pat" Mullins (Board of Supervisors), 1979 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - John P. Murphy, Jr. (Delegate), 1971 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Richard E. Murphy (Delegate-Democratic Conference, Delegate-Democratic National Committee), 1976 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Robert J. Murrin (State Senate), 1975 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Lauretta Newport (Delegate), 1977 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Oliver L. North (U.S. Senate), 1994 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Jerry W. Norton (Delegate), 1975 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Richard Dudley Obenshain (U.S. Senate), 1978 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Brendan P. O'Hara (Delegate), 1981 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Patrick O'Leary (Commonwealth Attorney), Undated (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Jean Packard (Chair-Board of Supervisors, State Senate), 1972-1979 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Stanford E. Parris (Chair-Board of Supervisors, Delegate, House of Representatives), Undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Benton Partin (Delegate), 1981 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Lawrence J. Pascal (Delegate), 1983 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Martha B. Pennino (House of Representatives), 1974 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Kelly A. Perdue (Board of Supervisors), Undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Ross Perot (President), 1992 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Martin H. Perper (Delegate), 1981 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - G. Conoly Phillips (U.S. Senate), 1978 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Rufus C. Phillips, III (Board of Supervisors, House of Representatives, U.S. Senate), 1971-1977 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Owen B. Pickett (Chair-State Democratic Party), 1981 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Kenneth R. Plum (Delegate), Undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Fred G. Pollard (Governor), 1969 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Patrick Portway (Delegate), 1971 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Lawrence D. Pratt (Delegate), 1979-1981 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Clifford H. Pruefer (Delegate), 1971 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Don Rapier (Delegate), Undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - George C. Rawlings, Jr. (U.S. Senate, Democratic National Committee), Undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Ronald Reagan (President), 1980 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Paul Reiber (Delegate), 1965 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Richard S. "Major" Reynolds (Lieutenant Governor), 1977 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Fred J. Ricci (House of Representatives), 1982 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Marie W. Ridder (Delegate), 1982 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Richard M. Riemer (Delegate), 1977 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - E. Stanley Rittenhouse (House of Representatives), 1976 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Charles S. Robb (Lieutenant Governor, Governor, U.S. Senate), Undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Thomas Jefferson Rothrock (Delegate), 1971-1977 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - John H. "Jack" Rust, Jr. (Delegate), Undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Thomas D. Rust (State Senate), 1979 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Richard J. Ryder (Delegate), 1969 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Richard L. Saslaw (Delegate, State Senate, House of Representatives), 1975-1984 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - David E. Satterfield, III (House of Representatives), 1970 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - John Scalamonti (Delegate), 1977 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - John T. Schell (Attorney General), 1977 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Beverly J. Schwarz (Delegate), 1979 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Eva Scott (State Senate), 1979 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - James M. Scott (Board of Supervisors), 1971 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - John L. Scott (State Senate), 1965 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Peter W. Scott (Delegate), 1979 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - William Scott (House of Representatives, U.S. Senate), 1966-1976 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - George W. Senge, Jr. (Delegate), Undated (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Pauline M. Shockency (Eighth Congressional District Democratic Committee), 1976 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Lawrence A. Short (Delegate), 1965 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Sargent Shriver (Vice President), 1972 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - George A. Simpson (Board of Supervisors), Undated (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Walter T. Skallerup (Delegate), 1969 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Myron C. "Mike" Smith (Delegate), 1969 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Ron Smith (State Senate), Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Erwin S. "Shad" Solomon (Attorney General), 1977 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Nancy B. Spannaus (Governor), 1993 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - William B. Spong (U.S. Senate), 1966-1972 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Nora Anderson Squyres (Delegate), 1982 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Bill Stanhagen (Board of Supervisors), 1967 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Darrel H. Stearns (House of Representatives), 1970 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Thomas G. Stewart (Eighth Congressional District Democratic Committee), 1976 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Christopher Stokes (Sheriff), 1979 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Eileen M. Stout (Delegate), 1977 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Vernon LeRoy "Lee" Strang, Jr. (Delegate), 1981 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - George W. Stroube (Delegate), 1975 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Robert J. Surovell (Delegate), 1971 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Marilyn Suskind (Delegate-Democratic National Convention), 1976 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Dave Sutherland (Delegate), 1969 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Robert Arnold Sweatt (Unknown), Undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - James D. Swinson (Sheriff), Undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - James R. Tate (House of Representatives, State Senate), 1976-1979 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - David L. Temple (Delegate), 1982 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - William Thaler (Board of Supervisors), 1967 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - John M. Thoburn (State Senate), Undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Robert Thoburn (Delegate, House of Representatives), 1976-1980 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Marie B. Travesky (Board of Supervisors), Undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Paul S. Trible, Jr. (U.S. Senate), 1982 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Dana Tucker (Board of Supervisors), 1974 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Morris Udall (President), 1976 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Drew Valentine (Delegate), Undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Raymond E. Vickery, Jr. (Delegate, State Senate, House of Representatives), Undated (Box 6, Folder 28)